Madeleine Harris

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/madeleine-m-harris/

Github: https://github.com/miss-mad/

portfolio

SUMMARY

New full stack web developer with a unique and varied background in healthcare, retail, event coordination, property management, accounting, and the fine arts. This wide array of experience culminates in a meticulous, disciplined, and ever-inquisitive fast learner. Excited to bring new technical and development skills, combined with existing knowledge and skill, to this flourishing field of web development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Git, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6 and CommonJS), SQL, NoSQL, GraphQL

Frameworks: CSS Frameworks (Materialize CSS, Bootstrap CSS), MySQL, Apollo

Libraries: jQuery, Sequelize, MongoDB and Mongoose, React

Core Concepts: Mobile-First Design, APIs (client, third-party, and server-side), Agile

Methodology, Github and Heroku Deployment

PROJECTS

Who's App

https://github.com/miss-mad/Whos-App | https://whooooos-app.herokuapp.com/

- The newest anonymous and secure messaging app is here! Who is it you'll be talking to?
- Role: Project manager + learned and implemented Socket.io (the core chat feature)
- Tools: Socket.io, JavaScript, Node, Express, Sequelize, MySQL, Handlebars, Bootstrap

MTHSY Music

https://github.com/miss-mad/mthsy-music | https://miss-mad.github.io/mthsy-music/

- A one-stop shop for music information and upcoming events for music artists
- Role: lastFM API + local storage
- Tools: JavaScript, HTML, Materialize CSS, APIs: lastFM, YouTube, TicketMaster

Bird's Eye for Business (will be replaced by the 3rd React project)

https://github.com/miss-mad/birds-eye-for-business | Link to Deployed Project

- Handy workplace manager with bird's eye perspectives built for businesses
- Role: Solo author
- Tools: JavaScript, Node, Inquirer, MySQL, dotenv

EXPERIENCE

Pharmacy Technician

2021 - Present

Walgreens

Highly communicative to patients of all ages to ensure timely medication requests' fulfillment while efficiently taking in new prescriptions, filling existing orders, and checking out waiting patients. Meticulously sorted the day's incoming order of medicines to ensure previously out of stock items are completed while also coordinating various vaccine appointments and COVID testing.

CME Coordinator 2019 – 2020

American Medical Forum

Repeatedly coordinated periodic medical conferences with hundreds of healthcare professional attendees.

Licensed Property Manager

2018 - 2019

HomeOwners Advantage

Project manager for the \$143,691 gym renovation June – September 2018.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: Georgia Institute of Technology